They're armed but she's dangerous.
The Pickup is a action, comedy, crime film directed by Tim Story.
A routine cash pickup takes a wild turn when mismatched armored truck drivers Russell and
Travis are ambushed by ruthless criminals led by savvy mastermind Zoe.
Russell, played by Eddie Murphy.
Travis, played by Pete Davidson.
Zoe, played by Keke Palmer.
Natalie, played by Eva Longoria.
Banner, played by Jack Kesy.
Miguel, played by Ismael Cruz Cordova.
The Pickup is a 2025 American heist action comedy film produced and directed
by Tim Story and written by Matt Mider and Kevin Burrows.
The film stars Eddie Murphy, Pete Davidson, Eva Longoria, and Keke Palmer.
The film was released by Amazon MGM Studios via Amazon Prime Video on
August 6, 2025, and received generally negative reviews.
The film explores themes of robbery, armored car,
organized crime, shootout, witty.
The tone is lighthearted.